var $jscomp=$jscomp||{};$jscomp.scope={};$jscomp.arrayIteratorImpl=function(a){var b=0;return function(){return b<a.length?{done:!1,value:a[b++]}:{done:!0}}};$jscomp.arrayIterator=function(a){return{next:$jscomp.arrayIteratorImpl(a)}};$jscomp.makeIterator=function(a){var b="undefined"!=typeof Symbol&&Symbol.iterator&&a[Symbol.iterator];return b?b.call(a):$jscomp.arrayIterator(a)};
var quiz=[{question:"\u30b2\u30fc\u30e0\u5e02\u5834\u3001\u3082\u3063\u3068\u3082\u58f2\u308c\u305f\u30b2\u30fc\u30e0\u6a5f\u306f\u6b21\u306e\u3046\u3061\u3069\u308c\uff1f",answers:["\u30b9\u30fc\u30d1\u30fc\u30d5\u30a1\u30df\u30b3\u30f3","\u30d7\u30ec\u30a4\u30b9\u30c6\u30fc\u30b7\u30e7\u30f3\uff12","\u30cb\u30f3\u30c6\u30f3\u30c9\u30fc\u30b9\u30a4\u30c3\u30c1","\u30cb\u30f3\u30c6\u30f3\u30c9\u30fcDS"],correct:"\u30cb\u30f3\u30c6\u30f3\u30c9\u30fcDS",description:"2004\u5e7411\u670824\u65e5\u767a\u58f2\u30012\u753b\u9762\u306e\u643a\u5e2f\u30b2\u30fc\u30e0\u6a5f"},
{question:"\u7cf8\u4e95\u91cd\u91cc\u304c\u4f01\u753b\u306b\u95a2\u308f\u3063\u305f\u3001\u4efb\u5929\u5802\u306e\u770b\u677f\u30b2\u30fc\u30e0\u3068\u3044\u3048\u3070\uff1f",answers:["MONSTER2","\u30b9\u30fc\u30d1\u30fc\u30de\u30ea\u30aa\u30d6\u30e9\u30b6\u30fc\u30ba","\u30b9\u30fc\u30d1\u30fc\u30c9\u30f3\u30ad\u30fc\u30b3\u30f3\u30b0","\u661f\u306e\u30ab\u30fc\u30d3\u30a3"],correct:"MONSTER2",description:"\u30cd\u30b9"},{question:"\u30d5\u30a1\u30a4\u30ca\u30eb\u30d5\u30a1\u30f3\u30bf\u30b8\u30fcIV\u306e\u4e3b\u4eba\u516c\u306e\u540d\u524d\u306f\uff1f",
answers:["\u30d5\u30ea\u30aa\u30cb\u30fc\u30eb","\u30af\u30e9\u30a6\u30c9","\u30c6\u30a3\u30fc\u30c0","\u30bb\u30b7\u30eb"],correct:"\u30bb\u30b7\u30eb",description:"\u30cd\u30b9"},{question:"\u30b9\u30bf\u30d0",answers:["\u30c9\u30c8\u30fc\u30eb","\u30b9\u30bf\u30fc\u30d0\u30c3\u30af\u30b9\u30b3\u30fc\u30d2\u30fc","\u30bf\u30ea\u30fc\u30ba\u30b3\u30fc\u30d2\u30fc","\u30b5\u30f3\u30de\u30eb\u30af"],correct:"\u30b9\u30bf\u30fc\u30d0\u30c3\u30af\u30b9\u30b3\u30fc\u30d2\u30fc",description:"\u30d5\u30e9\u30da\u30c1\u30fc\u30ce\u304c\u4eba\u6c17"},
{question:"2",answers:["2","\u30af\u30e9\u30a6\u30c9","\u30c6\u30a3\u30fc\u30c0","\u30bb\u30b7\u30eb"],correct:"2",description:"\u30cd\u30b9"},{question:"3",answers:["\u30d5\u30ea\u30aa\u30cb\u30fc\u30eb","3","\u30c6\u30a3\u30fc\u30c0","\u30bb\u30b7\u30eb"],correct:"3",description:"\u30cd\u30b9"},{question:"4",answers:["\u30d5\u30ea\u30aa\u30cb\u30fc\u30eb","\u30af\u30e9\u30a6\u30c9","4","\u30bb\u30b7\u30eb"],correct:"4",description:"\u30cd\u30b9"},{question:"5",answers:["\u30d5\u30ea\u30aa\u30cb\u30fc\u30eb",
"\u30af\u30e9\u30a6\u30c9","\u30c6\u30a3\u30fc\u30c0","5"],correct:"5",description:"\u30cd\u30b9"},{question:"6",answers:["\u30d5\u30ea\u30aa\u30cb\u30fc\u30eb","\u30af\u30e9\u30a6\u30c9","\u30c6\u30a3\u30fc\u30c0","6"],correct:"6",description:"\u30cd\u30b9"},{question:"\u30e2\u30f3\u30d9\u30eb",answers:["\u6d77","\u5c71","\u8349\u539f","\u8352\u91ce"],correct:"\u5c71",description:"\u5c71\u4ee5\u5916\u3082\u3042\u308b\u304b\u3082"},{question:"\u4e00\u756a\u7f8e\u5473\u3044\u306e\u306f",answers:["\u9b5a",
"\u305b\u3093\u3079\u3044","\u3068\u3046\u3075","\u30c1\u30e3\u30fc\u30cf\u30f3"],correct:"\u30c1\u30e3\u30fc\u30cf\u30f3",description:"\u5727\u5012\u7684"},{question:"\u9ec4\u8272\u3044\u679c\u7269\u306f",answers:["\u30d0\u30ca\u30ca","\u30ea\u30f3\u30b4","\u6843","\u3044\u3061\u3054"],correct:"\u30d0\u30ca\u30ca",description:"\u30a4\u30c1\u30b4\u30ea\u30f3\u30b4\u8d64\u3001\u6843\u30d4\u30f3\u30af"}];
function shuffle(a){for(var b=a.length-1;0<=b;b--){var c=Math.floor(Math.random()*(b+1)),d=$jscomp.makeIterator([a[c],a[b]]);a[b]=d.next().value;a[c]=d.next().value}return a}array=shuffle(quiz);console.log(quiz);
var quizLength=quiz.length,quizIndex=0,score=0,$button=document.getElementsByTagName("button"),buttonLength=$button.length,countNumber=1,setupQuiz=function(){document.getElementById("js-question").textContent=quiz[quizIndex].question;for(var a=0;a<buttonLength;)$button[a].textContent=quiz[quizIndex].answers[a],a++};setupQuiz();var count=function(){document.getElementById("count").textContent="\u7b2c"+countNumber+"\u554f"};count();
for(var handlerIndex=0;handlerIndex<buttonLength;)$button[handlerIndex].addEventListener("click",function(a){clickHandler(a)}),handlerIndex++;
var clickHandler=function(a){quiz[quizIndex].correct===a.target.textContent?(document.getElementById("js-answer").textContent="\u6b63\u89e3\uff01",setPopup(),score++):(document.getElementById("js-answer").textContent="\u6b8b\u5ff5\uff01\u6b63\u89e3\u306f"+quiz[quizIndex].correct,setPopup());quizIndex++;countNumber++},setPopup=function(){function a(e){e&&e.addEventListener("click",function(){b.classList.remove("is-show");if(5>quizIndex)setupQuiz(),count();else{var h=function(f){f&&f.addEventListener("click",
function(){g.classList.remove("is-show-result");location.reload()})},g=document.getElementById("js-popup-result");g.classList.add("is-show-result");var k=document.getElementById("js-black-bg2"),l=document.getElementById("js-close-btn2");0===score?document.getElementById("js-result").textContent=score+"/5 \u304c\u3093\u304c\u308c\uff01":5>score?document.getElementById("js-result").textContent=score+"/5 \u79c0\u624d\uff01\uff01":document.getElementById("js-result").textContent=score+"/5 \u5929\u624d\uff01\uff01\uff01";
h(k);h(l)}})}var b=document.getElementById("js-popup");if(b){b.classList.add("is-show");var c=document.getElementById("js-black-bg"),d=document.getElementById("js-close-btn");a(c);a(d);document.getElementById("js-description").textContent=quiz[quizIndex].description}},reloadBtn=document.getElementById("js-reload");reloadBtn.addEventListener("click",function(){location.reload()});